(Leonard:)And in the corner, chained to the wall,
you see a bloodied and beaten Santa Claus.
He says, "Ho, ho, help me."
(Howard:)Yes, we found Santa. Christmas is saved.
(Howard:)Don't ever tell my mother I said that.
(Stuart:)I take out my skeleton key
and run to Santa to unchain him.
(Sheldon:)But first I cast a spell of paralysis
on Stuart and Howard.
(Howard:)- What are you doing?
- Can't talk, you're paralyzed.
(Sheldon:)I get right up in Santa's big, fat face
and say:
"Well, well, well, Jolly old Saint Nick,
we meet again.
(Sheldon:)I believe the last time we spoke was
in the Baybrook Mall in Galveston, Texas...
...when I was 5 years old, isn't that right?"
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)My mother dragged me there
and plopped me down on your lap...
(Sheldon:)...and you asked me
what I wanted for Christmas.
(Sheldon:)I told you my Pop-Pop, because
that was the year my grandfather died.
(Sheldon:)I missed him and I wanted him back.